uwars.com 2006-12-18

# Universe Wars - Privacy Policy

The following refers to all services provided Universe Wars. We take your privacy seriously.

**INFORMATION:**  
All personal information is of your choosing to supply. Your IP address (Internet protocol), hostname and browser details are logged for administrative purposes. No supplied information such as email addresses are sold to third parties.

**CONTACT DETAILS:**  
Although not required, we need your full name, address and contact number for postage of prizes. This information is only used to make sure your prize arrives. If this information is not required we are unable to deliver your prize. You can choose not to supply it and if you do win a prize you can supply it at that point.

**SECURITY:**  
We use a form of encryption to mask your password, for the security of your account. You should never give out your password. This information is stored on your computer and our server(s), only.

**COOKIES:**  
We may use cookies to customize your experience while on the Universe Wars website. With all modern browsers you are able to specify whether you would like to reject or accept cookies, and even accept from a select few. Our 3rd party advertisers may use cookies to collect information and are subject to their own privacy policy.

**EMAIL:**  
Any email you may receive from Universe Wars will never ask for your password. Generally, we will not contact you directly, however depending on your "Account Settings" you may recieve email regarding important news and updates.

**COMMUNICATION:**  
Universe Wars offers chat rooms, private mail and message boards to communicate with the rest of our friendly community. Any personal information you may disclose via these areas can be viewed by any registered member or who you send the mail to and therefor due diligence should be taken. Again note that staff will never contact you requesting account details such your as username and password combination.

If you need any more information in regards to our Privacy Policy please use the Contact Us page.
